http://www.ulula.co.uk/privacypolicy.html

CatalogueMilk & FormulaBabyWeaningPreschoolFamilyAt HomeWellbeingFree FromBrandsOffers & PromotionsChristmasPrivacy Policy Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, and print and keep a copy of them for your reference regarding any order you may place with us today.At Ulula we never lose sight of the fact that our customers come first.  We are committed to protecting and respecting your personal data and privacy. This privacy and cookie policy relates to our use of any personal data we collect from you from any of our services. We collect information about you solely in order to process your order and to provide you with the best possible service. The personal information which we hold is held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law. Whenever you provide such information, we are legally obliged to use your information in line with all applicable laws concerning the protection of personal data; including the Data Protection Act 1998 (DPA) and The General Data Protection Regulation 2016 (GDPR) together, and with other subsequent laws “Data Protection Laws”. WHO WE ARE AND HOW TO CONTACT USFor the purpose of the Data Protection Laws, the data controller is Ulula. If you want to request more information about our privacy policy or information regarding data protection you should contact us using the details provided below:Chris Burdett UlulaRush FarmStockwoodWorcestershireB96 6SXinfo@ulula.co.uk01386 791027
YOUR RIGHTS
Under the GDPR your rights are: To be informed – We must make available this privacy notice with the emphasis on transparency over how we process your data. Access – You are entitled to find out what details we may hold about you and why. Rectification – We are obliged to correct or update your details. Erasure – This is also known as the request to be forgotten. Restrict processing – You have the right to ‘block’ or suppress the processing by us of your personal data. Data portability – You have the right to obtain and reuse your personal data that you have provided to us. Object – You have the right to object to us processing your data in relation to direct marketing and or profiling.
Rights in relation to automated decision making and profiling – We do not use automatic decision making or processing.
THE DATA WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU
We process Personal data. Personal data we process may include name, address and email address. It also may include IP address and cookies (Website).Our collection methods are: Through our website Through engagement of our services By communications Networking Through engagement of service providers
How Ulula Uses Cookies
Like most websites, Ulula uses cookies. Cookies are small text files in your browser that websites save to your computer. They are used to make our site work better for you, and to help us understand how people use the Ulula website. You can manage and/or delete these small files as you wish using your web browser settings. To learn more about cookies and how to manage them, visit www.AboutCookies.org.Ulula does NOT use cookies to track your movements across multiple websites. We do NOT accept third party advertising nor set cookies whose aim is to aid third party advertisers. We do NOT use cookies to store your personal information.
First Party Cookies
These are cookies that are set by this website directly and store basic data on your interactions with the Ulula website. For example, when a visitor clicks a tab on the tabbed box on the home page, the system sets a cookie to remember which tab you selected.As with many e-commerce websiters, the Ulula website sets temporary cookies to make our shopping basket system work. If you delete or disable those cookies you will not be able to shop on the Ulula website. No personal information is stored in cookies at any time.
Third Party Cookies
These are cookies set on your machine by external websites whose services are used on this site. The only third party cookies currently set on Ulula are from Google Analytics. Like many millions of websites, Ulula uses Google Analytics to anonymously collect information about how people use this site. We do this to help make sure it's meeting our customers' needs and to understand how we can do so better. Google Analytics stores anonymous information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. Google Analytics does not collect or store any personal information (e.g. your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are.
HOW YOUR DATA WILL BE USED
We use information held about you to:
Ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your devices;
Provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes or by Legitimate Interests;
Carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us;
Allow you to participate in interactive features of our service when you choose to do so, e.g. asking a question through our website.
Carry out necessary maintenance to our infrastructure; and
Notify you about changes to our services We also embrace the use of social media and may wish to process any comments made public by you
LEGITIMATE INTEREST & MARKETING
When you place an order with Ulula we will email you to confirm your order, and send another email when your order has been despatched.When you place an order with Ulula you agree to receive occasional emails from us to tell you about our products, services and special offers. Some offers are only available to Ulula customers.We use MailChimp as our marketing automation platform. By clicking below to submit this form, you acknowledge that the information you provide will be transferred to MailChimp for processing in accordance with their Privacy Policy and Terms.You will be able to unsubscribe at any time from the mailing list that we maintain for this purpose. To unsubscribe just follow the unsubscribe link at the bottom of every email and follow the simple instructions. You will not be re-added to the mailing list with subsequent orders, unless you specifically request it.Where we use Legitimate Interests we will record our decision and our method on making this decision. This can be requested by you at any time.If you are an existing contact or customer we will only contact you by postal and electronic means (e-mail) with information about services or goods which you have previously purchased from us or enquired about.
THIRD PARTIES
Information about you and your transactions will not be passed on to a third party, except to enable us to supply your ordered goods or to enable us to tell you about our services. For example, we provide your name, delivery address, email and phone number to our courier. A Data processing Agreement exists between Ulula and the third party fulfilment partners to ensure the process of Ulula data is in line with our conditions and the conditions of the GDPR data protection laws to ensure that this data will never be used for any purpose other than that for which it was given.Our current courier notifies customers via email when their parcel has been dispatched and provides parcel tracking details. Additionally, the courier sends customers two text messages regarding the progress of their parcel: one confirming that the parcel is out for delivery and the other letting you know the parcel has been either delivered, carded or left with a neighbour. If you wishes to opt out of either or both of these services please make a note in the 'Additional Information' field during checkout.A Data processing Agreement also exists between Ulula and our Data Controller to ensure the process of Ulula data is in line with our the GDPR data protection laws.
DATA RETENTION
Our data retention policy is dictated by the Data Protection Laws and is available for inspection by submitting a written request using the contact details provided in this policy.
DATA DELETION
Under GDPR you have the right to erasure under specific circumstances. A request for your personal data to be deleted will be decided on a case by case basis and must be submitted in writing to the contact details provided in this policy.
DATA CORRECTION
We will correct or update your data without delay provided you make the request in writing to the contact details provided in this policy, clearly specifying which data is incorrect or out of date.
DATA INSPECTION
We strive to be as open as we can be in terms of giving people access to their personal data. Individuals can find out if we hold any of their personal data by making a formal request under the Data Protection Laws. Such requests must be in writing to the contact details provided in this policy. If we do hold your personal data we will respond in writing within one calendar month of your request (where that request was submitted in accordance with this policy).
The information we supply will:
Confirm that your data is being processed;
Verify the lawfulness and the purpose of the processing;
Confirm the categories of personal data being processed;
Confirm the type of recipient to whom the personal data has been or will be disclosed, and
Let you have a copy of the data in an intelligible form.  Please note that you may need to provide identification in order to prove who you are to access your data.If you agree, we will try to deal with your request informally, for example by providing you with the specific information you need over the telephone.In the instance that we do not hold information about you we will also confirm this in writing at the earliest opportunity.
COMPLAINTS
You have the right to complain about the processing of your personal data. Please contact us using the details provided above. If you are still unsatisfied you have the right to complain to the Information Commissioners Office.
CHANGES TO THESE TERMS
The terms were last amended 25th May 2018 and apply from this date. We keep our privacy notice under regular review and you should check back regularly to ensure you are aware of changes to it. We may display this notice to you from time to time to help ensure you are aware of its contents.
Advice & ValuesWeaning AdviceWhy Organic?Allergy & HealthHome Made Recipes  Helpful ThingsContact UsRead Our BlogAll About UlulaDelivery & ReturnsTerms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicyPromotions & CompetitionsSitemap© 2020 Ulula.   eCommerce Software by BlueparkHomeMilkBabyNew Born +Organic Baby Milk FormulaOrganic TeasBaby BottlesOrganic Skin CareTeething & ColicMuslins & BibsEco Nappies & Essentials4 Months +Organic Baby Milk FormulaOrganic Baby Milk CerealsOrganic Baby Fruit JarsOrganic Baby Vegetable JarsOrganic Baby Meat JarsOrganic Baby Weaning OilOrganic TeasBaby BottlesOrganic Skin CareTeething & ColicMuslins & BibsEco Nappies & Essentials6 Months +Organic Baby Milk FormulaOrganic Baby PorridgesOrganic Baby Milk CerealsOrganic Baby Food PouchesOrganic Baby Fruit JarsOrganic Baby Vegetable JarsOrganic Baby Meat JarsOrganic Finger Foods & SnacksOrganic Baby Weaning OilOrganic TeasBaby BottlesOrganic Skin CareTeething & ColicMuslins & BibsEco Nappies & Essentials8 Months +Organic Baby Milk FormulaOrganic Baby PorridgesOrganic Baby Milk CerealsOrganic Baby Food PouchesOrganic Baby Fruit JarsOrganic Baby Vegetable JarsOrganic Baby Meat JarsOrganic Baby Weaning OilBaby BottlesOrganic Finger FoodsOrganic TeasOrganic Skin CareTeething & ColicMuslins & BibsOrganic Junior MuesliEco Nappies & Essentials12 Months +Growing up MilkPouches & SmoothiesBreakfast CerealsSavoury Snacks & RusksSugar Free SnacksPastaBaby BottlesTeething & ColicMuslins & BibsEco Nappies & EssentialsWeaningMilk Feeding & WeaningReady to Wean SignsStarting WeaningWeaning ChartAllergy Aware DietWeaning FAQsRecipes for BabyPreschoolOrganic Breakfast CerealsPure Fruit Organic Smoothies & DrinksOrganic Snacks & LunchboxesOrganic PastaFree From ChocolateFree From BiscuitsFamilyOrganic Cereals & MuesliOrganic PastaBaking & CookingOrganic Biscuits & CookiesOrganic SnacksFree From ChocolateFree From PastaOrganic ChocolateHomeBathroomKitchenPlayingEco Nappies & EssentialsWearNatural CleaningEatingDrinkingCelebrationsBagsPetsWellbeingTeethingOrganic Face MasksOrganic Baby & Kids Skin CareNatural Sun CareColicBruises, Cuts & ColdsTooth CarePregnancy & New MumsBreastfeedingElixirs & TeasNatural Face & Body CarePlastic Free Baby WipesFree FromGluten FreeLactose FreeDairy FreeBrandsHolleMOGLiHeveaWeledaAlb-GoldErdmannHAUSERBohlsener MillUnder the NileWooly OrganicMuslinZPura BottlesHohenfriedECOlunchboxKit & KinNatural Birthing CompanyJack N' JillFreskCocoa LocoBajoU KonserveFabelabEkoboPATCHRoobaAmbrosiusLittle Pasta OrganicsMama BambooTikiriChristmasAdvent Calendars & BooksChristmas Gifts for Little Ones (newborn to age 2)Christmas Gifts for Older Ones (age 2 to 5+)Organic Party Food & Festive TreatsFree From ChristmasStocking FillersWooden Games & JigsawsChristmas Soft ToysEco Building BlocksFestive Eco HomeParentsPetsOffersOffersCrumpled CornersShort DatedPromotions   View Basket | Wish List | New Account | Sign In
